[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What do you think will happen?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "will", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, I can't really predict but I think you're right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "really", "predict", "but", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cardinal O'Malley", "Cardinal Dolan"], "LOCATION": ["Boston", "New York"]}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Yes, and don't you love, by the way, Cardinal O'Malley out of Boston, Cardinal Dolan out of New York.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "do", "n't", "you", "love", ",", "by", "the", "way", ",", "Cardinal", "O'Malley", "out", "of", "Boston", ",", "Cardinal", "Dolan", "out", "of", "New", "York", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "So what is your sense about the kind of reform, which a new Pope may look to successfully push through?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "is", "your", "sense", "about", "the", "kind", "of", "reform", ",", "which", "a", "new", "Pope", "may", "look", "to", "successfully", "push", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "I would say there are really two areas.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "there", "are", "really", "two", "areas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Does he believe he has a chance?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "believe", "he", "has", "a", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I did speak to him yesterday.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "speak", "to", "him", "yesterday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "And how are you going to be more attractive and joyful than Cardinal Timothy Dolan?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "are", "you", "going", "to", "be", "more", "attractive", "and", "joyful", "than", "Cardinal", "Timothy", "Dolan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "But, also, I think the key word is energy.", "answer_tokens": ["But", ",", "also", ",", "I", "think", "the", "key", "word", "is", "energy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Timothy Dolan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "UINN: Nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["UINN", ":", "Nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Do you believe he's wrong about this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "he", "'s", "wrong", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "I do because my fear is, my belief is that with food-related issues, which are different, which are more complicated because unlike smoking which you can stop and continue existing, you have to interact with food at least three times a day.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "because", "my", "fear", "is", ",", "my", "belief", "is", "that", "with", "food-related", "issues", ",", "which", "are", "different", ",", "which", "are", "more", "complicated", "because", "unlike", "smoking", "which", "you", "can", "stop", "and", "continue", "existing", ",", "you", "have", "to", "interact", "with", "food", "at", "least", "three", "times", "a", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Are you giving me 100 percent guarantee you will not meddle in things that people eat or drink?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "giving", "me", "100", "percent", "guarantee", "you", "will", "not", "meddle", "in", "things", "that", "people", "eat", "or", "drink", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Do you have a view on the Pope, by the way?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "view", "on", "the", "Pope", ",", "by", "the", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "You know, you have to be for your hometown guy.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "you", "have", "to", "be", "for", "your", "hometown", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine Quinn"]}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Who would be the next mayor of New York?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "be", "the", "next", "mayor", "of", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Well, I am for Christine Quinn, but it's a wide open race.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "am", "for", "Christine", "Quinn", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "a", "wide", "open", "race", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "How did you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "UINN: It was great.", "answer_tokens": ["UINN", ":", "It", "was", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Have you thought about what yours might be?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "thought", "about", "what", "yours", "might", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, we -- when we launched the campaign -- actually we kicked it off with a walk and talk tour.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "--", "when", "we", "launched", "the", "campaign", "--", "actually", "we", "kicked", "it", "off", "with", "a", "walk", "and", "talk", "tour", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Say that again?", "question_tokens": ["Say", "that", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "A walk and talk.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "walk", "and", "talk", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "RP", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Do you believe in doing that, or is it purely on merit?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "in", "doing", "that", ",", "or", "is", "it", "purely", "on", "merit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "You know, I think you want to help folks move up, right, and the only way I got this job, my first job in New York City as tenant housing organizer, I called people.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "you", "want", "to", "help", "folks", "move", "up", ",", "right", ",", "and", "the", "only", "way", "I", "got", "this", "job", ",", "my", "first", "job", "in", "New", "York", "City", "as", "tenant", "housing", "organizer", ",", "I", "called", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What is the secret to getting to where you've got to?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "secret", "to", "getting", "to", "where", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Push ahead.", "answer_tokens": ["Push", "ahead", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Is she right that too many women lean back rather than lean in when it comes to promoting themselves and being ambitious?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "right", "that", "too", "many", "women", "lean", "back", "rather", "than", "lean", "in", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "promoting", "themselves", "and", "being", "ambitious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Well, hello, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "hello", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Are women basically a bit nicer than men in the workplace and does that consequentially hold them back?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "women", "basically", "a", "bit", "nicer", "than", "men", "in", "the", "workplace", "and", "does", "that", "consequentially", "hold", "them", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Yes, and yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marissa Mayer"]}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Or is Marissa Mayer going to be in the minority when most women want to have flexi time and maybe work a bit from home?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "Marissa", "Mayer", "going", "to", "be", "in", "the", "minority", "when", "most", "women", "want", "to", "have", "flexi", "time", "and", "maybe", "work", "a", "bit", "from", "home", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Marissa Mayer is in a very unique situation.", "answer_tokens": ["Marissa", "Mayer", "is", "in", "a", "very", "unique", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marissa Mayer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Wouldn't that help?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "that", "help", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Even when that's not possible -- I remember my chief of staff was pregnant with her baby, and I encouraged her, look, we work ridiculous hours in Congress, bring your daughter to work, we'll use the pack 'n play.", "answer_tokens": ["Even", "when", "that", "'s", "not", "possible", "--", "I", "remember", "my", "chief", "of", "staff", "was", "pregnant", "with", "her", "baby", ",", "and", "I", "encouraged", "her", ",", "look", ",", "we", "work", "ridiculous", "hours", "in", "Congress", ",", "bring", "your", "daughter", "to", "work", ",", "we", "'ll", "use", "the", "pack", "'n", "play", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "(on camera): This is a Bushmaster?", "question_tokens": ["(", "on", "camera", ")", ":", "This", "is", "a", "Bushmaster", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Were you surprised, Hillary, at the ease with which you bought that rifle?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", ",", "Hillary", ",", "at", "the", "ease", "with", "which", "you", "bought", "that", "rifle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Well, like you, I knew what the law was.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "like", "you", ",", "I", "knew", "what", "the", "law", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Are you an American citizen or resident?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "an", "American", "citizen", "or", "resident", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I am an American citizen and resident.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "an", "American", "citizen", "and", "resident", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "You could have been a British citizen and still done the same thing?", "question_tokens": ["You", "could", "have", "been", "a", "British", "citizen", "and", "still", "done", "the", "same", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Well, legally, you're supposed to be an American citizen.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "legally", ",", "you", "'re", "supposed", "to", "be", "an", "American", "citizen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "What did you do with it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "do", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "No, of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]